[Plot Love II]
[مؤامرة الحب الثاني]
[Episode 8]
[الحلقة 8]
Okay.
تمام.
Whatever.
ايا كان.
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
Don't forget our agreement.
لا تنسى اتفاقنا.
Only one question.
سؤال واحد فقط.
Is Su Bei your daughter?
هل سو باي ابنتك؟
Yes.
نعم.
She's my daughter with my ex-wife.
إنها ابنتي مع زوجتي السابقة.
But...
ولكن...
That's fine.
هذا جيّد.
She's the one I'm marrying.
هي التي سأتزوجها.
Gao Jiming.
جاو جيمنج.
See them out.
انظر لهم بالخارج.
Mr. Lu.
السيد.  شمس.
Ms. Su.
آنسة.  مع.
You'd better do your job well
من الأفضل أن تقوم بعملك بشكل جيد
and focus on the contest.
والتركيز على المسابقة.
Don't think about anything else.
لا تفكر في أي شيء آخر.
Manni. Manni.
رجل.  رجل.
Are we just leaving?
هل سنغادر للتو؟
How could such a good marriage
كيف يمكن لمثل هذا الزواج الجيد
be given to her?
لها؟
Enough, what's the use of regretting it now?
كفى ، ما فائدة الندم الآن؟
You were the one who forced me
كنت أنت من أجبرني
to ask for Su Bei.
لأطلب Su Bei.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
I did this for your good.
لقد فعلت هذا من أجل مصلحتك.
If Su Bei relies on the Lu family,
إذا كانت Su Bei تعتمد على عائلة Lu ،
what good will it do to you?
ما هو الخير لك؟
Enough.
كافية.
Lu Nan is mine.
لو نان لي.
I won't give up easily.
لن أستسلم بسهولة.
Sorry.
آسف.
I seem to
يبدو اني
have screwed up your birthday party.
لقد أفسدت حفلة عيد ميلادك.
I didn't mean to be late.
لم أقصد أن أتأخر.
I was locked in a room.
كنت محبوسا في غرفة.
Someone said you're going to surprise me.
قال أحدهم أنك ستفاجئني.
So I...
لذا أنا...
Sorry, Mr. Lu.
آسف ، السيد لو.
I am leaving.
أنا مغادر.
Here they are. Mr. Lu...
ها هم.  السيد لو ...
Ms. Su.
آنسة.  مع.
Could you explain
هل يمكن ان توضح
what happened at Mr. Lu's birthday party
ماذا حدث في حفلة عيد ميلاد السيد لو
just now?
الآن؟
Ms. Su.
آنسة.  مع.
Was the person who was supposed to marry Mr. Lu
كان الشخص الذي كان من المفترض أن يتزوج السيد لو
really Ms. Su Manni?
حقا السيدة  سو ماني؟
Yes.
نعم.
Explain it to us.
اشرحها لنا.
What is your relationship?
ما هي علاقتك؟
Everyone.
الجميع.
Su Bei
مع باي
is my fiancee.
هي خطيبتي.
Those who bully her
أولئك الذين يتنمرون عليها
are against me.
ضدي.
Nice.
لطيف - جيد.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Mr. Lu, say something.
السيد لو ، قل شيئا.
Thanks for helping me out.
شكرا لمساعدتي.
You are my fiancee.
أنت خطيبتي.
I have an obligation to protect you.
لدي التزام بحمايتك.
After all, we signed a contract.
بعد كل شيء ، وقعنا عقدا.
[The chaotic private life of Huanzhen's president]
[الحياة الخاصة الفوضوية لرئيس Huanzhen]
A few days ago,
منذ بضعة أيام،
at the birthday banquet of Lu Nan, the president of Huanzhen,
في مأدبة عيد ميلاد لو نان ، رئيس Huanzhen ،
there was a farce of two women fighting for one husband.
كانت هناك مهزلة لامرأتين تتقاتلان من أجل زوج واحد.
The private life of president of Huanzhen
الحياة الخاصة لرئيس Huanzhen
has sparked discussions among many netizens.
أثار مناقشات بين العديد من مستخدمي الإنترنت.
Grandma, don't listen to their nonsense.
الجدة ، لا تستمع إلى هرائهم.
Your brother's marriage
زواج أخيك
is my idea after all.
هي فكرتي بعد كل شيء.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Am I so impatient
هل أنا غير صبور
that matched the wrong couple?
التي تطابق الزوجين الخطأ؟
Grandma, it's not your fault.
الجدة ، هذا ليس خطأك.
You don't know how messy their family is.
أنت لا تعرف مدى فوضى عائلتها.
But if Ms. Su
ولكن إذا كانت السيدة سو
is really like what her younger sister said,
يشبه حقًا ما قالته أختها الصغرى ،
I think
أظن
she is quite smart.
انها ذكية جدا.
It's not smart,
انها ليست ذكية ،
but sophisticated.
لكنها متطورة.
Grandma, don't worry.
جدتي ، لا تقلقي.
I will ask for my brother.
سأطلب أخي.
Grandma, calm down.
جدتي ، اهدئي.
Mr. Ye, did you come back from Milan
سيد يي ، هل عدت من ميلان
for the Angel's Covenant Costume Contest
لمسابقة زي العهد الملائكي
this time?
هذا الوقت؟
Would you accept the sponsor's invitation
هل تقبل دعوة الراعي
to be a judge of the competition?
ليكون حكما في المسابقة؟
Mr. Ye.
السيد.  هو.
Where is Ting?
أين تينغ؟
She still doesn't want to go home?
ما زالت لا تريد العودة إلى المنزل؟
No.
رقم.
She's really spoiled.
انها حقا مدللة.
Mr. Ye.
السيد.  هو.
Four companies would like to invite you
أربع شركات تود دعوتك
to participate in the design guidance of this costume contest.
للمشاركة في توجيه تصميم مسابقة الأزياء هذه.
They have contacted me many times.
لقد اتصلوا بي عدة مرات.
Try to reject them.
حاول رفضهم.
I don't want to get involved in this contest.
لا أريد المشاركة في هذه المسابقة.
Aren't you satisfied with any of these?
ألا تشعر بالرضا عن أي من هؤلاء؟
What is the theme of this municipal proposition contest?
ما هو موضوع مسابقة الاقتراح البلدية هذه؟
The ocean.
المحيط.
What's your idea?
ما هي فكرتك؟
I have searched for a lot of information online.
لقد بحثت عن الكثير من المعلومات على الإنترنت.
But I don't think
لكنني لا أعتقد
my design
تصميمي
is good enough for the contest.
هو جيد بما فيه الكفاية للمسابقة.
Are you under
هل أنت تحت
too much pressure?
كثير من الضغط؟
In fact, many creative ideas
في الواقع ، العديد من الأفكار الإبداعية
come from inspiration.
يأتي من الإلهام.
No matter how complete the information on the Internet is,
بغض النظر عن مدى اكتمال المعلومات الموجودة على الإنترنت ،
it is not as good as the experience of being there.
إنها ليست جيدة مثل تجربة التواجد هناك.
Yes.
نعم.
Grandma.
الجدة.
About what happened at Lu Nan's birthday party...
حول ما حدث في حفلة عيد ميلاد لو نان ...
Nan told me everything.
أخبرني نان بكل شيء.
It was Gao Jiming who came to propose marriage.
كان جاو جيمينغ هو من جاء ليقترح الزواج.
He didn't reveal my identity at all.
لم يكشف عن هويتي على الإطلاق.
You have been away from home for a long time.
لقد كنت بعيدًا عن المنزل لفترة طويلة.
If they hadn't come to you,
إذا لم يأتوا إليك ،
how could you possibly know about it?
كيف يمكن أن تعرف عنها؟
So the truth of the matter
إذن حقيقة الأمر
has come to light.
ظهرت للضوء.
Right.
الصحيح.
Thank you for believing in me.
شكرا للاعتقاد في لي.
The most important thing for you right now
أهم شيء بالنسبة لك الآن
is to develop feelings.
هو تنمية المشاعر.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
when could I have a great-grandchild?
متى يمكن أن يكون لي ابن حفيد؟
Take some water.
خذ بعض الماء.
I bought two tickets for an art exhibition.
اشتريت تذكرتين لمعرض فني.
I heard that designers
سمعت أن المصممين
are most interested in this.
هم الأكثر اهتمامًا بهذا.
Nan, go with Bei.
نان ، اذهب مع باي.
I...
أنا...
Grandma, I've been busy with a contest recently.
جدتي ، لقد كنت مشغولاً بمسابقة مؤخرًا.
I'm going to Starlight Island this afternoon.
أنا ذاهب إلى جزيرة ستارلايت بعد ظهر اليوم.
I've bought the ticket.
لقد اشتريت التذكرة.
So I can't make it to the exhibition.
لذا لا يمكنني الحضور إلى المعرض.
Starlight Island...
جزيرة ستارلايت ...
It's beautiful there.
إنه جميل هناك.
But
ولكن
it's dangerous for you to go alone.
من الخطر أن تذهب بمفردك.
Ask Nan to go with you.
اطلب من نان أن يذهب معك.
Grandma.
الجدة.
I still have some work to do.
لا يزال لدي بعض العمل لأقوم به.
So...
لذا...
I know
أنا أعرف
how much work you have.
كم لديك من العمل.
Don't use work as an excuse.
لا تستخدم العمل كعذر.
You have to go together.
عليك أن تذهب معا.
Okay, grandma.
حسنًا ، جدتي.
- What about...?
- ماذا عن...؟  - ماذا عن...؟
- You first.
- أنت أولاً.  - أنت أولاً.
- I will go with you. - You should go to work.
- سوف اذهب معك.  - يجب أن تذهب إلى العمل.
Don't worry about the contest.
لا تقلق بشأن المسابقة.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
لا تضغط على نفسك كثيرًا.
The sea in my mind
البحر في ذهني
is quiet.
هادئة.
But today I feel that
لكني أشعر بذلك اليوم
the sea
البحر
is actually full of passion.
هو في الواقع مليء بالعاطفة.
Dear tourists,
السائحون الأعزاء ،
due to today's typhoon, swimming in the sea is prohibited.
بسبب إعصار اليوم ، السباحة في البحر محظورة.
Swimming in the sea is prohibited.
السباحة في البحر ممنوعة.
Please follow our lead.
يرجى اتباع قيادتنا.
It looks like we can't go back today.
يبدو أننا لا نستطيع العودة اليوم.
Dear tourists,
السائحون الأعزاء ،
due to today's typhoon, swimming in the sea is prohibited.
بسبب إعصار اليوم ، السباحة في البحر محظورة.
Swimming in the sea is prohibited.
السباحة في البحر ممنوعة.
Please follow our lead.
يرجى اتباع قيادتنا.
Gao Jiming, book me two rooms.
جاو جيمينج ، احجز لي غرفتين.
There's only one room left?
هل بقيت غرفة واحدة فقط؟
♪Another♪
♪ آخر ♪
♪Long talk all night♪
♪ حديث طويل طوال الليل ♪
♪I haven't finished drinking the water on the table♪
لم أنتهي من شرب الماء على المائدة
♪I stare at the windowsill♪
أحدق في حافة النافذة
♪That fallen flower is no longer blooming♪
♪ تلك الزهرة الساقطة لم تعد تتفتح
♪You always say♪
♪ أنت دائما تقول ♪
♪Like and love♪
♪ اعجاب وحب ♪
♪Are similar but different♪
♪ متشابهة لكنها مختلفة ♪
♪Finally this time I'm being depended on too♪
♪ أخيرًا هذه المرة أنا أعتمد أيضًا
♪Listen and cover up, learn to sigh♪
♪ استمع وتستر وتعلم التنهد ♪
♪How happy you are laughing♪
♪ ما مدى سعادتك بالضحك
♪You are planning your future with her♪
♪ أنت تخططين لمستقبلك معها
♪I'm so numb, but I'm♪
♪ أنا مخدر جدًا ، لكنني ♪
♪Still listening♪
♪ ما زلت تستمع ♪
♪I don't have to guess your mind anymore♪
♪ ليس عليّ أن أخمن عقلك بعد الآن ♪
♪Is it funny, sad or helpless♪
♪ هل هو مضحك أم حزين أم عاجز ♪
♪Adults shouldn't lose their temper easily♪
♪ لا ينبغي أن يفقد البالغون أعصابهم بسهولة ♪